{
    "id": "29e97aac28e24343bc5db2eba3bed742",
    "title": "If Or Unless",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. we don’t start now, we will be late.",
            "description": "We use if to express condition - something which must happen first so that something else can happen.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c9425497e57e476b8dd7200831044108"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you mend your ways, you will land in serious trouble.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. The given sentence can also be written as: If you do not mend your ways, you will land in serious trouble. ",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a48961b2b5a14508849dacae733c3be2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you don’t know the meaning of a word, you should look it up in the dictionary.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf3b1fcca07446029b1f382a0687e1d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t be able to do it ……………………….. your help.",
            "description": "Without means in the absence.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "02d4b849758347519b25f03a2f34ec9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not be able to do it …………………………… you do not help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "655475584ff24400985d0561484a218b"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you help me, I will not be able to do it.",
            "description": "Unless means if not.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d41c97748b43496fa5dd9c0505e12c20"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you have a wonderful memory, it is important to repeat your answers.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b36e9f52e38b41118c1f663f538b106b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not easy to get a job ………………………… you have experience.",
            "description": "The sentence means that ‘If you do not have experience, it is not easy to get a job.’",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32999715caaa4b9a946252af946be568"
        },
        {
            "question": "You cannot login ………………………….. you know the password.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc55fce05aec4acbbf8e94a9c811dccc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Children should not play with these toys ………………………….. they are under the supervision of an adult.",
            "description": "Unless means if not.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "without",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "98fef66ac0af43cab8e1f205f478959c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. she cannot come and see us, we will go and see her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05887e0501c74d409f5810716db931e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most wild animals do not attack people ……………………. they do not provoke them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9f830de356e457886fdc375163f9023"
        }
    ]
}